freeawesome.com 2016-11-24

# Free Awesome - Privacy Policy

**Policy Last Revised: July 3, 2012.**

The following sets forth the policies for the collection and use of personally identifiable information ("Information") by MGT Studios, Inc. dba FreeAwesome ("FreeAwesome") in connection with its operation of its Web site located at http://www.freeawesome.com (the "Site"), and supersedes any previous statement of such policies. FreeAwesome know that users' personal information is important to them, and that it is important that FreeAwesome respect that importance and treat that information responsibly. FreeAwesome has created the below policy to explain the types of information it collects from users, how it uses this information, with whom and for what purposes it shares the information, and how users can interact with FreeAwesome in connection with the information collection and use. FreeAwesome takes its obligations regarding privacy very seriously, and it wants to ensure users are fully informed about the Information they are providing to it.

**Collection of Information.**

In connection with the Site, FreeAwesome may collect Information in the following ways:

  * Through forms filled out by a user on the Site
  * Through Information provided by a user in connection with prize promotion entries
  * Through entries made by the user in blogs and other forums on the Site
  * Through the maintenance and analysis of Web server logs
  * Via e-mail and other communications between a user and FreeAwesome
  * Through the use by FreeAwesome of third-party databases from which user Information is extracted and combined with Information obtained by FreeAwesome through other means.

FreeAwesome may also connect non-personally identifiable information from users via "cookies" (small text files placed by FreeAwesome on user computers), single-pixel GIF image files (also called "Web beacons"), Web server log analysis and other similar technological means. Such information may be used to track site trends and enhance the user experience, and may be shared with third parties.

To the extent third parties may place advertising on the Site, such third parties may utilize cookies or other technological means within the advertising to collect and utilize non-personally identifiable information. FreeAwesome is not responsible for information collected by third parties in this manner, nor for the collection or use of Information by other sites to which the Site is linked.

**Types of Information Collected by FreeAwesome.**

The following types of Information about a user are among those that may be collected by FreeAwesome in connection with the Site:

  * Name
  * Postal address
  * E-mail address
  * Telephone number
  * Cell phone number
  * Facsimile number
  * Income range
  * Personal interests
  * Date of birth
  * IP Address
  * Referring site
  * Other technical information collected by the Site's servers.

**No Collection of Information from Children.**

The Site is not intended for users under the age of 18, nor does FreeAwesome knowingly collect or retain Information in connection with the Site from children under the age of 13.

**Use of Information.**

FreeAwesome may use Information collected in connection with the Site in the following ways:

  * To provide requested information, products and services to users via the Site or through other online or offline channels
  * To enable users to enter prize promotions and receive prizes from FreeAwesome and/or third parties
  * To improve the user experience with the Site
  * In connection with the operation of the Site
  * For users to obtain information and offers for products and services offered by FreeAwesome as well as selected third parties.

In order to do the foregoing, FreeAwesome may provide the Information to trusted third parties, including but not limited to selected third party marketers and vendors as well as third party contractors providing services to FreeAwesome such as the operation of the Site, communication services and fulfillment of orders, and credit card verification and payment services. All email you receive from FreeAwesome.com will be from FreeAwesome. FreeAwesome will use commercially reasonable efforts to limit use of the Information by such third parties to the specific uses set forth above. FreeAwesome also utilizes electronic and physical security to reduce the risk of improper access to or manipulation of Information during transmission and storage, but cannot guarantee the security or integrity of the Information and shall have no liability for breaches of security or integrity or third-party interception in transit.

FreeAwesome may also disclose Information when it determines it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or regulations, in connection with a merger, acquisition, asset purchase or sale of or by FreeAwesome, or to protect the interests or safety of FreeAwesome, its customers, or other visitors to the Site.

**Opting Out from Offers from FreeAwesome.**

At any time, a user may opt out from receiving future offers from FreeAwesome through the user's profile on the Site, by following the instructions contained within each marketing communication or by sending an e-mail message to remove@freeawesome.com. Such opting out will not apply to any communications from third parties to whom FreeAwesome may have provided Information regarding the user. Third parties' use of the Information is subject to such parties' own privacy policies, for which FreeAwesome shall not be responsible.

**Access to Information.**

All users who provide their Information to FreeAwesome may modify and correct such Information through their personal profile on the Site.

**Your California Privacy Rights.**

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of FreeAwesome who are California residents to request certain information regarding FreeAwesome's disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties' direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to: FreeAwesome, 500 Mamaroneck Ave, Suite 204, Harrison, NY 10528.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy.**

FreeAwesome reserves the right to revise and update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such revisions will be effective on the date of posting to the Site, and will apply to all information collected by FreeAwesome both prior to and following the effective date. Your use of the Site following any such revisions will be deemed your acceptance of such revisions. Users should periodically visit this page to review the current policies with regard to Information.
